

#### **PROFILE**

I am a student at the University of Memphis majoring in Computer Engineering with 3 years of programming experience. I also have 7 years of musical experience playing the trombone in various places around the world. I am a dedicated, hardworking, organized, reliable person who can work his way through any problem presented to him.

#### CONTACT

PHONE:

+1 (901) 283-5999

WEBSITE: Jrwright.me

EMAIL:

wright.jordanr@tmfmail.us

## **HOBBIES**

Trombone Player PC Builder Coder

#### **SKILLS**

Dedicated, Hardworking, Organized, Reliable, Flexible, and Responsible.

## **OFFICE SKILLS**

Windows, Macintosh, Linux, Networking, Coding, and Microsoft Office Applications

# JORDAN R. WRIGHT

Student

## **EDUCATION**

## **Bolton High School**

August 2014 – May 2016 Member of Bolton HS Band.

## **Bartlett High School**

August 2016 – May 2018 Graduated Top 20%. Member of Bartlett HS Band. Member of Music Honor Society. GPA: 3.9

## **University of Memphis**

August 2018 – May 2022 Studying to obtain a bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering. GPA: 3.4

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## STAX Music Academy - Trombone Player

September 2014 – May 2018

Trombone Player for Rhythm Section and Jazz Ensemble and Trombone Player for 2017 STAX European Tour.

## Christian Brothers University - Jr. CEO

July 2015

This was a summer internship program where I learned entry level skills on how start and maintain a business.

## Memphis Grizzles/NBA – Trombone Player/Actor

May 2016

Played Trombone on the original track for Craig Brewer's Short Film and actor among the Orchestra in Craig Brewer's Short Film.

## Memphis Police Department - Vehicle Detailer

July 2016

I worked with the Memphis Police Department under JMJ's Mobile Vehicle Detailing Service cleaning police vehicles.

## Bellevue Baptist Church - Trombone Player

September 2017 – Present

Member of the Bellevue Baptist Orchestra performing music for the church and at events around the city.

## Temple of Deliverance – Substitute Trombone Player

January 2019 - Present

I fill in for trombone players who are unable to play on Sundays.